A Guide to the Rockefeller Foundation records, general correspondence, RG 2, 1981-1990 FA402
Rockefeller Archive Center
- General Correspondence, 1982; 0.52 Cubic Feet 39 microfilm reels (35mm); 39 Reels 39 microfilm reels (35mm)
  - United States, 1982; 1982/200
    - Michigan State University, Hamilton Ruth S. (Supplementary Material), 1982 (Reel 19, Frame 1)
    - Michigan State University (B-W), 1982 (Reel 19, Frame 464)
    - Mi-Mu, 1982 (Reel 19, Frame 584)
    - National (A), 1982 (Reel 19, Frame 872)
    - National (B-C), 1982 (Reel 20, Frame 1)
    - National Federation of State Humanities Councils, 1982 (Reel 20, Frame 428)
    - National (E-F), 1982 (Reel 20, Frame 547)
    - National (G-I), 1982 (Reel 20, Frame 888)
    - National (L-O), 1982 (Reel 21, Frame 1)
    - National Rural Fellows, 1982 (Reel 21, Frame 285)
    - National (P-S), 1982 (Reel 21, Frame 402)
    - National Urban League (Stafford, Walter W.), 1982 (Reel 22, Frame 1)
    - National Urban League (J-W), 1982 (Reel 22, Frame 349)
    - National Women's Employment and Education, Inc., 1982 (Reel 22, Frame 597)
    - National Women's Employment and Education, Inc. (Supplementary Material), 1982 (Reel 22, Frame 825)
    - National Women's Law Center (Greenberger, Marcia D.), 1982 (Reel 23, Frame 1)
    - Na, 1982 (Reel 23, Frame 180)
    - New (D-W), 1982 (Reel 23, Frame 219)
    - New York City (A-H), 1982 (Reel 23, Frame 432)
    - New York University (L-W), 1982 (Reel 23, Frame 525)
    - New York (L-W), 1982 (Reel 23, Frame 631)
    - Ne, 1982 (Reel 23, Frame 843)
    - Ni-Nu, 1982 (Reel 23, Frame 860)
    - Oklahoma State University (C-M), 1982 (Reel 23, Frame 1010)
    - Oregon State University (K-W), 1982 (Reel 24, Frame 1)
    - O, 1982 (Reel 24, Frame 39)
    - Pan American Health Organization, 1982 (Reel 24, Frame 341)
    - Partners of the Americas, 1982 (Reel 24, Frame 723)
    - Pennsylvania State University (A-L), 1982 (Reel 24, Frame 917)
    - Pa-Pi, 1982 (Reel 24, Frame 942)
    - Ph - Po, 1982 (Reel 25, Frame 1)
    - Princeton University (B-T), 1982 (Reel 25, Frame 303)
    - Princeton University (Urban Research), 1982 (Reel 25, Frame 359)
    - Princeton University (von Hippel, Frank), 1982 (Reel 25, Frame 675)
    - Project Awareness (Teenage Pregnancy), 1982 (Reel 25, Frame 931)
    - Pr - Pu, 1982 (Reel 25, Frame 1053)
    - Q, 1982 (Reel 26, Frame 1)
    - Ra, 1982 (Reel 26, Frame 57)
    - Re, 1982 (Reel 26, Frame 252)
    - Ri, 1982 (Reel 26, Frame 622)
    - Rockefeller, 1982 (Reel 26, Frame 634)
    - Ro - Ru, 1982 (Reel 26, Frame 847)
    - Sa-Sc, 1982 (Reel 27, Frame 1)
    - Se-Sh, 1982 (Reel 27, Frame 293)
    - Smithsonian Institution (Ellsworth, Gretchen G.), 1982 (Reel 27, Frame 443)
    - Si-Sm, 1982 (Reel 27, Frame 553)
    - So, 1982 (Reel 27, Frame 614)
    - Stanford University (A-W), 1982 (Reel 27, Frame 1060)
    - State University of New York (B-S), 1982 (Reel 28, Frame 1)
    - Sp - Sy, 1982 (Reel 28, Frame 111)
    - Texas A&M University (H-M), 1982 (Reel 28, Frame 281)
    - Ta - Te, 1982 (Reel 28, Frame 319)
    - Th - To, 1982 (Reel 28, Frame 522)
    - Tr - Tw, 1982 (Reel 28, Frame 680)
    - United States, Agency for International Development (A-Y), 1982 (Reel 28, Frame 758)
    - United States, Agriculture (B-T), 1982 (Reel 28, Frame 1021)
    - United States, House of Representatives (Reuss, Henry S.), 1982 (Reel 29, Frame 1)
    - United States (E-L), 1982 (Reel 29, Frame 174)
    - United States (S), 1982 (Reel 29, Frame 231)
    - United States Committee on International Youth Year, 1982 (Reel 29, Frame 279)
    - United States Helsinki Watch Committee, 1982 (Reel 29, Frame 289)
    - United States News and World Report, 1982 (Reel 29, Frame 484)
    - University of California (D-W), 1982 (Reel 29, Frame 491)
    - University Of Chicago (F-S), 1982 (Reel 29, Frame 690)
    - University (A-K), 1982 (Reel 29, Frame 803)
    - University of Michigan (G-S), 1982 (Reel 29, Frame 1025)
    - University of Minnesota (A-R), 1982 (Reel 30, Frame 1)
    - University of Notre Dame (H-S), 1982 (Reel 30, Frame 123)
    - University of Pennsylvania (B-W), 1982 (Reel 30, Frame 266)
    - University of Pennsylvania (B-W), 1982 (Reel 30, Frame 380)
    - University of Texas (C-S), 1982 (Reel 30, Frame 483)
    - University (M-W), 1982 (Reel 30, Frame 539)
    - Urban Institute (Economic Policy Conference), 1982 (Reel 30, Frame 774)
    - U, 1982 (Reel 31, Frame 1)
    - V, 1982 (Reel 31, Frame 402)
      Scope and Contents
      Includes correspondence to/from Stanley Vanderbeek.
    - WGBH (A-O), 1982 (Reel 31, Frame 635)
    - WNET/Thirteen (H-Y), 1982 (Reel 31, Frame 923)
    - Williams, Franklin H., 1982 (Reel 32, Frame 1)
    - Wiliams, Roger John, 1982 (Reel 32, Frame 138)
    - Williams, Roger John (Supplementary Marterial), 1982 (Reel 32, Frame 353)
    - W - Wi, 1982 (Reel 32, Frame 524)
    - World Institute of Black Administrators (Williams, Terrie B.), 1982 (Reel 32, Frame 750)
    - Wo-Wu, 1982 (Reel 33, Frame 1)
    - Yale University (African American Employment), 1982 (Reel 33, Frame 203)
    - Yale University (E-R), 1982 (Reel 33, Frame 309)
    - Y-Z, 1982 (Reel 33, Frame 325)
    - United States - Medical Sciences, 1982; 1982/200.A
      - Harvard University (Medical School), 1982 (Reel 33, Frame 472)
  - Philippines, 1982; 1982/242
    - International Federation of Agricultural Research Systems Development, 1982 (Reel 33, Frame 621)
    - I-T, 1982 (Reel 33, Frame 688)
  - Virgin Islands, 1982; 1982/257
    United States Virgin Islands
    - Caribbean Center for Understanding Media, 1982 (Reel 33, Frame 744)
  - Playwrights in Residence, 1982; 1982/272
    - A-M, 1982 (Reel 33, Frame 763)
    - N-W, 1982 (Reel 33, Frame 1020)
  - South America, 1982; 1982/300
    - H - I, 1982 (Reel 34, Frame 1)
    - South America - Medical Sciences, 1982; 1982/300.A
      - A - V, 1982 (Reel 34, Frame 155)
  - Argentina, 1982; 1982/301
    - Argentina (Reel 34)
  - Bolivia, 1982; 1982/303
    Bolivia
    - Flores C., Gonzalo, 1982 (Reel 34, Frame 193)
  - Brazil, 1982; 1982/305
    - A - U, 1982 (Reel 34, Frame 233)
    - Brazil - Fellowships, 1982; 1982/305.E
      - C - Z, 1982 (Reel 34, Frame 327)
  - Chile, 1982; 1982/309
    - Academy of Christian Humanism, 1982 (Reel 34, Frame 362)
    - B - L, 1982 (Reel 34, Frame 652)
  - Colombia, 1982; 1982/311
    - A - U, 1982 (Reel 34, Frame 681)
    - Colombia - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1982; 1982/311.D
      - Colombian Agriculture Institute (Samper, Armando), 1982 (Reel 34, Frame 917)
  - Costa Rica, 1982; 1982/313
    Costa Rica
    - I - U, 1982 (Reel 34, Frame 920)
  - Haiti, 1982; 1982/320
    Haiti
    - Management Services for Health (Rohde, Jon E.), 1982 (Reel 34, Frame 969)
  - Mexico, 1982; 1982/323
    - Northeast Agricultural Research Center, 1982 (Reel 34, Frame 982)
    - A-Z, 1982 (Reel 35, Frame 1)
    - Mexico - Fellowships, 1982; 1982/323.E
      - Bautista-Garfias, Carlos Ramon, 1982 (Reel 35, Frame 98)
  - Peru, 1982; 1982/331
    - Instituto de Estudios Peruanos (Matos Mar, Jose), 1982 (Reel 35, Frame 158)
    - Peru - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1982; 1982/331.D
      - Agriculture, 1982 (Reel 35, Frame 199)
  - Dominican Republic, 1982; 1982/335
    - Medina Gonzales, Onesimo, 1982 (Reel 35, Frame 431)
  - Uruguay, 1982; 1982/337
    Uruguay
    - C-L, 1982 (Reel 35, Frame 477)
  - Venezuela, 1982; 1982/339
    Venezuela
    - Pulido, Pablo A., 1982 (Reel 35, Frame 635)
  - England, 1982; 1982/401
    - Management, Agricultural Services, Development, and Research, 1982 (Reel 35, Frame 779)
    - B-Q, 1982 (Reel 35, Frame 913)
    - University of Southhampton (A-H), 1982 (Reel 36, Frame 1)
    - R-W, 1982 (Reel 36, Frame 111)
  - Australia, 1982; 1982/410
    - A-U, 1982 (Reel 36, Frame 273)
  - Caribbean Region and Central America, 1982; 1982/420
    - D-G, 1982 (Reel 36, Frame 430)
  - Guyana, 1982; 1982/423
    Guyana
    - Nascimento, Christopher A., 1982 (Reel 36, Frame 449)
  - Canada, 1982; 1982/427
    - Husereau, Yvon, 1982 (Reel 36, Frame 457)
    - B-W, 1982 (Reel 36, Frame 888)
    - York University (Ontario), 1982 (Reel 37, Frame 1)
  - Hong Kong, 1982; 1982/463
    - Jian Hua Foundation, 1982 (Reel 37, Frame 49)
  - India, 1982; 1982/464
    - A - S, 1982 (Reel 37, Frame 90)
  - Pakistan, 1982; 1982/465
    - Smythe, Cheves Mc C., 1982 (Reel 37, Frame 852)
  - Malaysia, 1982; 1982/473
    - A - S, 1982 (Reel 37, Frame 856)
  - Nepal, 1982; 1982/474
    - Subedi, Laksmi Prasad, 1982 (Reel 37, Frame 864)
  - Africa, 1982; 1982/475
    - Council of Directors of Economic and Social Research Institute in Africa, 1982 (Reel 37, Frame 871)
  - Kenya, 1982; 1982/476
    - M - O, 1982 (Reel 37, Frame 911)
  - Rhodesia, 1982; 1982/483
    Zimbabwe
    - S- U, 1982 (Reel 37, Frame 923)
  - Uganda, 1982; 1982/492
    - M - O, 1982 (Reel 37, Frame 933)
  - West Africa, 1982; 1982/495
    - B-R, 1982 (Reel 38, Frame 1)
  - Ghana, 1982; 1982/496
    - Twum-Baah, Kwaku, 1982 (Reel 38, Frame 341)
  - Nigeria, 1982; 1982/497
    - B-U, 1982 (Reel 38, Frame 416)
  - France, 1982; 1982/500
    - C-O, 1982 (Reel 38, Frame 453)
  - Asia, 1982; 1982/600
    Asia
    - Asian Congress on Nutrition, 1982 (Reel 38, Frame 543)
  - China, 1982; 1982/601
    - J-T, 1982 (Reel 38, Frame 557)
    - China - Medical Sciences, 1982; 1982/601.A
      - Medical Education, 1982 (Reel 38, Frame 627)
    - China - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1982; 1982/601.D
      - Agriculture, 1982 (Reel 38, Frame 638)
  - Taiwan, 1982; 1982/605
    - Asian Vegetable Research and Development Center, 1982 (Reel 38, Frame 684)
  - Japan, 1982; 1982/609
    - M-S, 1982 (Reel 38, Frame 687)
  - Korea, 1982; 1982/613
    Korea
    - A-Y, 1982 (Reel 38, Frame 756)
  - Thailand, 1982; 1982/617
    - A-U, 1982 (Reel 38, Frame 823)
  - Holland, 1982; 1982/650
    - O-U, 1982 (Reel 38, Frame 870)
  - Indonesia, 1982; 1982/652
    - A-M, 1982 (Reel 38, Frame 898)
    - Indonesia - Fellowships, 1982; 1982/652.E
      - Sugiyarto, 1982 (Reel 38, Frame 958)
  - Belgium, 1982; 1982/707
    - N-S, 1982 (Reel 38, Frame 960)
  - Belgian Congo, 1982; 1982/709
    - M-T, 1982 (Reel 39, Frame 1)
  - Denmark, 1982; 1982/713
    Denmark
    - The Danish Institute for Clinical Epidemiology, 1982 (Reel 39, Frame 115)
  - Germany, 1982; 1982/717
    - D-G, 1982 (Reel 39, Frame 121)
  - Tanganyika, 1982; 1982/723
    - M-U, 1982 (Reel 39, Frame 132)
  - Italy, 1982; 1982/751
    - Centro di Ricerca e Documentazione, 1982 (Reel 39, Frame 150)
    - C-I, 1982 (Reel 39, Frame 506)
  - Liberia, 1982; 1982/759
    Liberia
    - Tarr, Byron, 1982 (Reel 39, Frame 528)
  - Morocco, 1982; 1982/765
    Morocco
    - African Training and Research Centre in Administration for Development, 1982 (Reel 39, Frame 559)
  - Norway, 1982; 1982/767
    - The Christian Michelsen Institute (Faaland, Just), 1982 (Reel 39, Frame 585)
  - Portugal, 1982; 1982/773
    - Instituto de Estudos Para o Desenvlvimento, 1982 (Reel 39, Frame 587)
  - Poland, 1982; 1982/789
    - C-F, 1982 (Reel 39, Frame 609)
  - Switzerland, 1982; 1982/803
    - D-V, 1982 (Reel 39, Frame 625)
  - Turkey, 1982; 1982/805
    - E-G, 1982 (Reel 39, Frame 690)
    - Turkey - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1982; 1982/805.D
      - Agriculture, 1982 (Reel 39, Frame 763)
  - Egypt, 1982; 1982/812
    - Egyptian-American Friendship Association, 1982 (Reel 39, Frame 771)
  - Jordan, 1982; 1982/816
    Jordan
    - Abdul Hameed Shoman Foundation, 1982 (Reel 39, Frame 791)
  - Syria, 1982; 1982/820
    Syria
    - Al-Khammas, A.M., 1982 (Reel 39, Frame 798)
  - Israel, 1982; 1982/825
    - A-R, 1982 (Reel 39, Frame 811)
  - Members and Meetings, 1982; 1982/903
    - H-W, 1982 (Reel 39, Frame 1012)
  - Humanities, 1982/911
    - Humanities - Fellowships, 1982; 1982/911.E
      - Kinkley, Jeffrey C., 1982 (Reel 39, Frame 1032)
      - A-L, 1982 (Reel 39, Frame 1071)
      - M-S, 1982 (Reel 39, Frame 1359)
      - T-W, 1982 (Reel 39, Frame 1554)
- General Correspondence, 1983; 0.34 Cubic Feet 26 microfilm reels (35mm); 26 Reels 26 microfilm reels (35mm)
  - International, 1983; 1983/100
    - Borlaug, Norman E., 1983 (Reel 1, Frame 1)
    - Lyman, Richard W., American Council on Education, Business (Higher Education Forum), 1983 (Reel 1, Frame 190)
    - Lyman, Richard W., Massachusetts Institute of Technology (Corporation Visiting Committee for Sponsored Research), 1983 (Reel 1, Frame 648)
    - Lyman, Richard W. (Recommendations), 1983 (Reel 2, Frame 1)
    - Rachi, Kenneth O., 1983 (Reel 2, Frame 89)
    - A - H, 1983 (Reel 2, Frame 193)
    - J - L, 1983 (Reel 2, Frame 436)
    - M - P, 1983 (Reel 2, Frame 738)
    - R - Y, 1983 (Reel 2, Frame 860)
  - Requests for Information, 1983; 1983/102
    - Bell, James F. 3rd, 1983 (Reel 2, Frame 1134)
  - International Organizations, 1983; 1983/103
    - International Bank (Lele, Uma), 1983 (Reel 2, Frame 1158)
    - International (B-U), 1983 (Reel 3, Frame 1)
    - Network of Community-Oriented Educational Institutions for Health Sciences, 1983 (Reel 3, Frame 374)
    - United Nations (D-W), 1983 (Reel 3, Frame 483)
    - United Nations Conference on Trade Development (MacIntyre, Alistair), 1983 (Reel 3, Frame 736)
    - United Nations Educational Scientific and Cultural Organization, 1983 (Reel 3, Frame 741)
    - United Nations Research Institute for Social Development, 1983 (Reel 3, Frame 754)
    - United Nations University (W), 1983 (Reel 3, Frame 777)
    - A-E, 1983 (Reel 3, Frame 811)
    - W, 1983 (Reel 3, Frame 908)
    - International Organizations - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1983; 1983/103.D
      - International Society for Plant Molecular Biology, 1983 (Reel 3, Frame 1019)
  - International Potato Program (IPP), 1983; 1983/107
    - International Potato Program, 1983 (Reel 3, Frame 1034)
  - Bellagio Study and Conference Center, 1983; 1983/120
    - A-P, 1983 (Reel 3, Frame 1036)
  - Conflict in International Relations, Declinations, 1983; 1983/155
    - Royal Institute of International Affairs (Europe, United States, and the Middle East), 1983 (Reel 4, Frame 1)
    - A-T, 1983 (Reel 4, Frame 136)
  - Equal Opportunity - Basic Rights/Policy Research, 1983/175
    - Equal Opportunity - Basic Rights/Policy Research - Fellowships, 1983; 1983/175.E
      - B-V, 1983 (Reel 4, Frame 588)
  - Special Interests and Explorations - Immigrants, 1983; 1983/181
    - A-G, 1983 (Reel 4, Frame 677)
    - K-W, 1983 (Reel 4, Frame 960)
  - United States, 1983; 1983/200
    - Alternatives to War, 1983 (Reel 5, Frame 1)
    - American (A-W), 1983 (Reel 5, Frame 78)
    - Association of American Colleges (Humanities and Careers in Business Conferences), 1983 (Reel 5, Frame 553)
    - Association for Rural Aid in Medicine, 1983 (Reel 5, Frame 650)
    - Ac-Ax, 1983 (Reel 5, Frame 940)
    - Bank Street College of Education (Granger, Robert C.), 1983 (Reel 5, Frame 1137)
    - Ba - Be, 1983 (Reel 6, Frame 1)
    - Bi - Bl, 1983 (Reel 6, Frame 228)
    - Bo - Bu, 1983 (Reel 6, Frame 370)
    - Carnegie Foundation (Aging Work Force Conference), 1983 (Reel 6, Frame 549)
    - Case Western Reserve University (Biomedical Literature), 1983 (Reel 6, Frame 807)
    - Ca, 1983 (Reel 6, Frame 949)
    - Center for Corporate Public Involvement, 1983 (Reel 7, Frame 1)
    - Center (A-T), 1983 (Reel 7, Frame 70)
    - Church Alternative (Investment Conference), 1983 (Reel 7, Frame 212)
    - Ch-Cl, 1983 (Reel 7, Frame 397)
    - Columbia University (B-L), 1983 (Reel 7, Frame 493)
    - Cooperative Assistance Fund, 1983 (Reel 7, Frame 516)
    - Cornell University (Rhodes, Frank H.), 1983 (Reel 7, Frame 614)
    - Coro Foundation, 1983 (Reel 7, Frame 638)
    - Co, 1983 (Reel 7, Frame 687)
    - Cr-Cu, 1983 (Reel 8, Frame 1)
    - Da-De, 1983 (Reel 8, Frame 35)
    - Di-Dn, 1983 (Reel 8, Frame 330)
    - Do-Du, 1983 (Reel 8, Frame 440)
    - Ea-Ed, 1983 (Reel 8, Frame 629)
    - Em-Eq, 1983 (Reel 8, Frame 778)
    - Ev-Ex, 1983 (Reel 8, Frame 944)
    - Fisk University (Great Issues Seminar), 1983 (Reel 9, Frame 1)
    - Ford Foundation (B-T), 1983 (Reel 9, Frame 131)
    - Fa-Fo, 1983 (Reel 9, Frame 347)
    - Fr-Fu, 1983 (Reel 9, Frame 510)
    - Ga-Gr, 1983 (Reel 9, Frame 612)
    - Harvard University (Education), 1983 (Reel 9, Frame 723)
    - Harvard University (B-W), 1983 (Reel 9, Frame 839)
    - Ha, 1983 (Reel 9, Frame 985)
    - He-Hi, 1983 (Reel 10, Frame 1)
    - Hornig, Lilli S., 1983 (Reel 10, Frame 75)
    - Howard University (E-W), 1983 (Reel 10, Frame 643)
    - Ho-Hu, 1983 (Reel 10, Frame 697)
    - Institute (C-S), 1983 (Reel 10, Frame 816)
    - International Centre for Ethnic Studies, 1983 (Reel 10, Frame 1055)
    - International Fertility Research Program, 1983 (Reel 11, Frame 1)
    - I, 1983 (Reel 11, Frame 569)
    - Jackson, W. Sherman, 1983 (Reel 11, Frame 720)
    - J, 1983 (Reel 11, Frame 1023)
    - K, 1983 (Reel 12, Frame 1)
    - LaGuardia community College (Archives/Social Studies Teaching), 1983 (Reel 12, Frame 321)
    - La-Lu, 1983 (Reel 12, Frame 450)
    - M-Mc, 1983 (Reel 12, Frame 834)
    - Me-Mi, 1983 (Reel 13, Frame 1)
    - Mo-Mu, 1983 (Reel 13, Frame 279)
    - National Academy of Science (B-T), 1983 (Reel 13, Frame 381)
    - National Action Council for Minorities in Engineering, 1983 (Reel 13, Frame 676)
    - National Action Council for Minoritites in Engineering (Supplementary Material), 1983 (Reel 13, Frame 680)
    - National (A-B), 1983 (Reel 14, Frame 1)
    - National Commission on the Social Role of the Federal Government (Pifer, Alan), 1983 (Reel 14, Frame 116)
    - National (C), 1983 (Reel 14, Frame 405)
    - National (E-I), 1983 (Reel 14, Frame 875)
    - National (L-O), 1983 (Reel 15, Frame 1)
    - National (P-U), 1983 (Reel 15, Frame 170)
    - Navajo Nation (Zah, Peterson), 1983 (Reel 15, Frame 406)
    - Neinaber, Katherine L., 1983 (Reel 15, Frame 464)
    - New (D-W), 1983 (Reel 15, Frame 470)
    - New York (A-P), 1983 (Reel 15, Frame 696)
    - New York University (Leontief, Wassily), 1983 (Reel 15, Frame 946)
    - New York University (M-U), 1983 (Reel 16, Frame 1)
    - Ni-Nu, 1983 (Reel 16, Frame 111)
    - O, 1983 (Reel 16, Frame 205)
    - Pa-Ph, 1983 (Reel 16, Frame 566)
    - President's Task Force for Private Sector Initiatives (January-February), 1983 (Reel 16, Frame 883)
    - President's Task Force for Private Sector Initiatives (March-May), 1983 (Reel 17, Frame 1)
    - President's Task Force for Private Sector Initiatives (June-September), 1983 (Reel 17, Frame 309)
    - President's Task Force for Private Sector Initiatives (October-December), 1983 (Reel 17, Frame 600)
    - President's Task Force for Private Sector Initiatives (Supplementary Matierial) [2 folders], 1983 (Reel 18, Frame 1)
    - Pr, 1983 (Reel 18, Frame 937)
    - Pu, 1983 (Reel 19, Frame 1)
    - Radcliffe College (Bunting Institute), 1983 (Reel 19, Frame 245)
    - Radcliffe College (Support Systems and American Women), 1983 (Reel 19, Frame 492)
    - Ra-Rh, 1983 (Reel 19, Frame 777)
    - Rockefeller, 1983 (Reel 19, Frame 914)
    - Ro-Ru, 1983 (Reel 19, Frame 1009)
    - Sa-Sc, 1983 (Reel 20, Frame 1)
    - Si-Sm, 1983 (Reel 20, Frame 301)
    - State University of New York (Wharton, Clifton R., Jr.), 1983 (Reel 20, Frame 507)
    - So-Su, 1983 (Reel 20, Frame 597)
    - Ta, 1983 (Reel 20, Frame 758)
    - Temple University (Video Exchange and Schools), 1983 (Reel 20, Frame 856)
    - Te-Tw, 1983 (Reel 21, Frame 1)
    - United States (A-S), 1983 (Reel 21, Frame 112)
    - University (A), 1983 (Reel 21, Frame 490)
    - University of California, Lawrence Hall of Science (Equals Program), 1983 (Reel 21, Frame 643)
    - University of California, Lawrence Hall of Science, Equals Program (Supplementary Material), 1983 (Reel 21, Frame 660)
    - University (C), 1983 (Reel 21, Frame 723)
    - University (D-I), 1983 (Reel 21, Frame 800)
    - University (M), 1983 (Reel 22, Frame 1)
    - University of Pennsylvania (N-W), 1983 (Reel 22, Frame 194)
    - University of Pittsburgh (International Studies), 1983 (Reel 22, Frame 380)
    - University (R-V), 1983 (Reel 22, Frame 496)
    - U, 1983 (Reel 22, Frame 565)
    - Washington International School (Goodman, Dorothy), 1983 (Reel 22, Frame 693)
    - Williams, Franklin H., 1983 (Reel 22, Frame 786)
    - Wo-Wi, 1983 (Reel 22, Frame 918)
    - Wo, 1983 (Reel 22, Frame 1012)
    - Yale University (E-S), 1983 (Reel 23, Frame 1)
    - Y-Z, 1983 (Reel 23, Frame 316)
    - United States - Humanities and Arts, 1983; 1983/200.R
      - Young Men's & Women's Hebrew Association - Poetry Contest, 1983 (Reel 23, Frame 537)
  - Philippines, 1983; 1983/242
    - F-K, 1983 (Reel 23, Frame 512)
  - Puerto Rico, 1983; 1983/243
    Puerto Rico
    - University of Puerto Rico (Liu, Eli-Jang), 1983 (Reel 23, Frame 637)
  - Playwrights in Residence, 1983; 1983/272
    - A-T, 1983 (Reel 23, Frame 641)
  - South America, 1983/300
    - South America - Medical Sciences, 1983; 1983/300.A
      - Pan American Federation of Associations of Medical Schools, 1983 (Reel 23, Frame 705)
  - Argentina, 1983; 1983/301
    - Argentina Medical Research (Ciarrapico, Norberto), 1983 (Reel 23, Frame 745)
  - Brazil, 1983; 1983/305
    - A-U, 1983 (Reel 23, Frame 747)
  - Colombia, 1983; 1983/311
    - A-U, 1983 (Reel 23, Frame 867)
    - Granados, Guido, 1983 (Reel 23, Frame 917)
  - Costa Rica, 1983; 1983/313
    - Costa Rica (Reel 23)
  - Haiti, 1983; 1983/320
    - Boucard, Adrien L., 1983 (Reel 23, Frame 921)
  - Mexico, 1983; 1983/323
    - O-U, 1983 (Reel 23, Frame 930)
    - Mexico - Ministry of Health, 1983 (Reel 23, Frame 958)
    - Mexico - Medical Sciences, 1983; 1983/323.A
      - Mexico (Reel 23)
  - Panama, 1983; 1983/327
    - Gorgas Memorial Institute, 1983 (Reel 23, Frame 982)
  - Peru, 1983; 1983/331
    - Latin American Council (Roca, Santiago), 1983 (Reel 23, Frame 1051)
  - Dominican Republic, 1983; 1983/335
    - National Council of Population and Family, 1983 (Reel 24, Frame 1)
  - England, 1983; 1983/401
    - I-U, 1983 (Reel 24, Frame 158)
    - England - Fellowships, 1983; 1983/401.E
      - C-S, 1983 (Reel 24, Frame 371)
  - Australia, 1983; 1983/410
    - A-R, 1983 (Reel 24, Frame 483)
  - Canada, 1983; 1983/427
    - J-S, 1983 (Reel 24, Frame 533)
  - Bahamas, 1983; 1983/433
    Bahamas
    - Eldon, Michael, 1983 (Reel 24, Frame 607)
  - Jamaica, 1983; 1983/437
    - Ena Thomas Memorial Trust (Hall, John A. S.), 1983 (Reel 24, Frame 626)
  - Hong Kong, 1983; 1983/463
    - University of Hong Kong, (Ko, Roland C.), 1983 (Reel 24, Frame 637)
  - India, 1983; 1983/464
    - A-M, 1983 (Reel 24, Frame 641)
  - New Guinea and Papua, 1983; 1983/472
    Papua New Guinea
    - Institute of Medical Research (Papua New Guinea), 1983 (Reel 24, Frame 723)
  - Malaysia, 1983; 1983/473
    - Statistics, 1983 (Reel 24, Frame 735)
  - Nepal, 1983; 1983/474
    - International Center for Integrated Mountain Development, 1983 (Reel 24, Frame 739)
  - Africa, 1983; 1983/475
    - Association for the Advancement of Agricultural Sciences in Africa, 1983 (Reel 24, Frame 823)
  - Kenya, 1983; 1983/476
    - K-N, 1983 (Reel 24, Frame 830)
    - University of Nairobi (Mukras, Mohammed), 1983 (Reel 24, Frame 844)
  - East Africa Region, 1983; 1983/477
    - Organization for Social Science Research in Eastern Africa, 1983 (Reel 25, Frame 1)
  - Malawi, 1983; 1983/482
    Malawi
    - Bunda College of Agriculture- Makhambera, 1983 (Reel 25, Frame 50)
  - Rhodesia, 1983; 1983/483
    - N-U, 1983 (Reel 25, Frame 55)
  - South Africa Region, 1983; 1983/487
    - M-U, 1983 (Reel 25, Frame 139)
  - Sudan, 1983; 1983/494
    - Health, 1983 (Reel 25, Frame 186)
  - West Africa, 1983; 1983/495
    - M-W, 1983 (Reel 25, Frame 210)
  - Nigeria, 1983; 1983/497
    - University of Ibadan (A-C), 1983 (Reel 25, Frame 313)
    - D-U, 1983 (Reel 25, Frame 556)